🎶
Wake up at 7 o'clock
just how it's supposed to be
and keep a radiant smile
so the others see
Work on a regular pace
when someone tells you to
Can't you obey?
What is so wrong with you?
Why can't I be like them?
I have tried to befriend them
I feel like it's nature that drives me away from
your designs
what you like
what you talk
what you strive
I can't imagine being like you
I don't believe in your bible
Repeat all your cycles
Yeah
The way you live is only causing me pain
Your life's so dull
I could never
But claim you know better
Why am I the one that's getting punished for it?
I am divergent
creative
come give it a try
If I told you how to behave, you'd know the suffering of mine
I don't believe you are better
No spirit
no ember
But, you surely know making my life into hell
🎶
I take a moment to see what you all speak about
But every time there's a smile
You just creep me out
I don't condone in the styles
but keep it to myself
and I don't need any form of your help
Why can't I live in peace?
You just dig underneath
I can't go on my life without hearing
my fault in
my designs
what I like
what I talk
what I strive
I can't be little different from you
I don't believe in your bible
Repeat all your cycles
Yeah
The way you live is only causing me pain
Your life's so dull
I could never
But claim you know better
Why am I the one that's getting punished for it?
I am divergent
creative
come give it a try
If I told you how to behave you'd know the suffering of mine
I don't believe you are better
No spirit
no ember
But, you surely know making my life into hell
🎶
Ooh, I'm so different
I don't believe in your bible
repeat all your cycles
Yeah
The way you live is only causing me pain
Your life's so dull
I could never
But claim you know better
Why am I the one that's getting punished for it?
I am divergent
creative
come give it a try
If I told you how to behave, you'd know the suffering of mine
I don't believe you are better
No spirit
no ember
But, you surely know making my life into hell
🎶